[Common]
ApplicationName="Epson ScanSmart"
InstallFolderPath=%ProgramFiles%\EPSON Software\Epson ScanSmart
SilentInstall=/qn
Installer=SETUP.EXE

RunServerOS=0

LastFirmVer=0
PrinterOnline=0

DefaultInstall=1
UpdateOnly=0

LocalInstaller="%AppPath%ScanSmart"

UpdateName="ScanSmartCore"
UpdateCTI=61

SupportOS="Winnt61;Winnt61.x64;Winnt62;Winnt62.x64;Winnt63;Winnt63.x64;Winnt100;Winnt100.x64"

[DownloadCheckInfo]
ApproveRegionCodeList="ApproveAll"
IgnoreRegionCodeList="0xF4,0x27"

[ApplicationDescription]
English="Scan the original document, then follow the onscreen instructions to save or send the scanned image."


Japanese="ウィザード形式で、スキャンした画像の保存や送信ができるアプリケーションです。"
German="Scannen Sie das Vorlagendokument und befolgen Sie dann die Bildschirmanweisungen zum Speichern und Versenden des gescannten Bildes."
French="Numérisez le document original, puis suivez les instructions affichées à l'écran pour enregistrer ou envoyer l'image numérisée."
Spanish="Digitalice el documento original y, a continuación, siga las instrucciones de la pantalla para guardar o enviar la imagen digitalizada."
Italian="Eseguire la scansione del documento originale, quindi seguire le istruzioni su schermo per salvare o inviare l'immagine acquisita."
Portuguese="Digitalize o documento original e, em seguida, siga as instruções apresentadas no ecrã para guardar ou enviar a imagem digitalizada."
Dutch="Scan het originele document, en volg vervolgens de instructies op het scherm voor het opslaan of verzenden van de gescande afbeelding."
Danish="Scan det original dokument, og følg derefter instruktionerne på skærmen, for at gemme og sende det scannede billede."
Swedish="Skanna originaldokumentet och följ sedan instruktionerna på skärmen för att spara eller skicka den sparade bilden."
Greek="Σαρώστε το πρωτότυπο έγγραφο και ακολουθήστε τις οδηγίες στην οθόνη για να αποθηκεύσετε ή να στείλετε τη σαρωμένη εικόνα."
Polish="Zeskanuj oryginalny dokument, a następnie wykonaj instrukcje ekranowe, aby zapisać lub wysłać zeskanowany obraz."
Finnish="Skannaa alkuperäinen asiakirja ja tallenna tai lähetä skannattu asiakirja näytön ohjeiden mukaisesti."
Czech="Oskenuje originální dokument a potom oskenovaný obrázek uloží nebo odešle podle zobrazených pokynů."
Turkish="Orijinal belgeyi tarayın, ardından taranan görüntüyü kaydetmek veya göndermek için ekrandaki talimatları izleyin."
Hungarian="Szkennelje be az eredeti dokumentumot, majd kövesse a képernyőn megjelenő utasításokat a szkennelt kép mentése és küldése érdekében."
Romanian="Scanaţi documentul original, apoi urmaţi instrucţiunile de pe ecran ca să salvaţi sau să trimiteţi imaginea scanată."
Russian="Отсканируйте оригинал документа, а затем следуйте инструкциям на экране, чтобы сохранить или отправить отсканированное изображение."
Norwegian="Skann originaldokumentet, og følg instruksjonene på skjermen for å lagre eller sende det skannede bildet."
Arabic="امسح المستند الأصلي ضوئيًا ثم اتبع التعليمات المعروضة على الشاشة لحفظ الصورة الممسوحة ضوئيًا أو إرسالها."
Slovak="Naskenujte originálny dokument a potom naskenovaný obraz uložte alebo odošlite podľa pokynov na obrazovke."
Ukraninan="Відскануйте оригінальний документ і дотримуйтеся вказівок на екрані, щоб зберегти або надіслати відскановане зображення."
Latvian="Skenējiet oriģinālo dokumentu un tad izpildiet ekrānā redzamos norādījumus, lai saglabātu vai nosūtītu skenēto attēlu."
Estonian="Skannige originaal ja seejärel järgige kuvatavaid juhiseid skannitud kujutise salvestamiseks või edastamiseks."
Lithuanian="Nuskaitykite originalų dokumentą, paskui, vykdydami ekrane pateikiamus nurodymus, nuskaitytą vaizdą įrašykite arba išsiųskite."
Bulgarian="Сканирайте оригиналния документ, след което следвайте инструкциите на екрана, за да запишете или изпратите сканираното изображение."
Hebrew="סרוק את המסמך המקורי ופעל לפי ההוראות המוצגות כדי לשמור או לשלוח את התמונה הסרוקה."
Korean="원본 문서를 스캔한 후 화면 지침에 따라 스캔된 이미지를 저장하거나 보냅니다."
Simplified Chinese="扫描原始文档，然后按照屏幕上的说明保存或发送扫描图像。"
Traditional Chinese(Taiwan)="掃描原稿，然後依照螢幕上的指示儲存或傳送掃描影像。"
Thai="สแกนเอกสารต้นฉบับ จากนั้นทำตามคำแนะนำบนหน้าจอเพื่อบันทึกหรือส่งภาพที่สแกน"
Malay="Imbas dokumen asal, kemudian ikuti arahan pada skrin untuk menyimpan atau menghantar imej yang diimbas."
Indonesian="Pindai dokumen asli, lalu ikuti petunjuk di layar untuk menyimpan atau mengirim gambar yang dipindai."
Vietnamese="Scan tài liệu gốc rồi thực hiện theo các hướng dẫn trên màn hình để lưu hoặc gửi hình scan."
Canadian French="Numériser le document original, puis suivre les directives à l'écran pour enregistrer ou envoyer l'image numérisée."
Mexican Spanish="Escanee el documento original, luego siga las instrucciones que aparecen en pantalla para guardar o enviar la imagen escaneada."
Brazilian Portuguese="Digitalize o documento original e depois siga as instruções na tela para salvar ou enviar a imagem digitalizada."
