[Common]
ApplicationName="Document Capture Pro"
InstallFolderPath=%ProgramFiles%\Epson Software\Document Capture
SilentInstall=/qn
Installer=SETUP.EXE

RunServerOS=0

LastFirmVer=0

PrinterOnline=0

DefaultInstall=0
UpdateOnly=0

LocalInstaller="%AppPath%DocumentCapture"

UpdateName="DCP2"
UpdateCTI=61

[Japanese]
ApplicationName="Document Capture Pro"

[ApplicationDescription]
Japanese="スキャナーから原稿を読み込んで画像を確認後、パソコン保存/ メール送信/ 印刷/ FTP サーバー転送などの操作ができます。"
English="This software allows you to perform various tasks after scanning an image and checking the file, such as saving the image to your computer, sending it by e-mail, printing, or uploading to an FTP server."
French="Ce logiciel vous permet d'effectuer différentes tâches une fois une image numérisée et le fichier vérifié : enregistrer l'image sur votre ordinateur, l'envoyer par courrier électronique, l'imprimer ou la télécharger vers un serveur FTP, par exemple."
German="Mit diesem Programm können Sie nach dem Scannen eines Bildes und Prüfen der Datei verschiedene Aufgaben durchführen, wie z. B. das Bild auf dem Computer speichern, per E-Mail versenden, drucken oder auf einen FTP-Server hochladen."
Dutch="Met deze software kunt u diverse taken uitvoeren na het scannen van een afbeelding en het controleren van het bestand. U kunt de afbeelding bijvoorbeeld opslaan op uw computer, verzenden per e-mail, afdrukken of uploaden naar een FTP-server."
Italian="Questo software consente di eseguire diverse attività dopo la scansione di un'immagine e la verifica del file, ad esempio il salvataggio dell'immagine sul computer, l'invio tramite email, la stampa o il caricamento su un server FTP."
Spanish="Este software le permite realizar diversas tareas después de escanear una imagen y revisar el archivo, tareas tales como guardar la imagen en su ordenador, enviarla por correo electrónico, imprimirla o cargarla en un servidor FTP."
Portuguese="Este software permite executar várias tarefas após digitalizar uma imagem e verificar o ficheiro, como guardar a imagem no seu computador, enviá-la por e-mail, imprimi-la ou transferi-la para um servidor FTP."
Turkish="Bu yazılım, bir görüntünün taranmasının ardından dosya kontrol edildikten sonra, görüntünün bilgisayara kaydedilmesi, e-posta ile gönderilmesi, yazdırılması veya bir FTP sunucusuna yüklenmesi gibi çeşitli işlemlerin gerçekleştirilmesini sağlar."
Greek="Το λογισμικό αυτό σας επιτρέπει να πραγματοποιείτε διάφορες εργασίες μετά τη σάρωση μιας εικόνας και τον έλεγχο του αρχείου, όπως το να αποθηκεύσετε την εικόνα στον υπολογιστή, να τη στείλετε μέσω e-mail, να την εκτυπώσετε ή να την μεταφορτώσετε σε έναν διακομιστή FTP."
Slovenian="S to programsko opremo lahko, potem ko optično preberete sliko in pregledate datoteko, izvedete različne naloge, kot so shranjevanje slike na računalnik, pošiljanje po e-pošti, tiskanje ali nalaganje slike na strežnik FTP."
Croatian="Ovaj softver Vam omogućava obavljanje različitih zadataka nakon skeniranja slike i provjeru datoteke, kao što je pohranjivanje slike na računalo, slanje putem e-pošte, ispisivanje, ili učitavanje na FTP poslužitelj."
Macedonian="Овој софтвер ви овозможува да вршите разни задачи откако ќе сканирате некоја слика и ќе го проверите фајлот, како сочувување на сликата на компјутерот, праќање по ел. пошта, печатење или праќање на FTP-server."
Serbian="Ovaj softver vam omogućava da posle skeniranja slike i provere datoteke obavite razne zadatke poput memorisanja slike na računaru, slanja slike e-poštom, štampanja ili slanja slike na FTP server."
Danish="Denne software gør det muligt at udføre forskellige opgaver efter scanning af et billede og kontrol af filen, f.eks. lagring af billedet på computeren, afsendelse af billedet som e-mail, udskrivning eller overførsel af billedet til en FTP-server."
Finnish="Tämä ohjelmisto mahdollistaa useiden toimintojen suorittamisen kuvan skannauksen ja tiedoston tarkistuksen jälkeen. Kuva voidaan esimerkiksi tallentaa tietokoneelle, lähettää sähköpostitse, tulostaa tai ladata FTP-palvelimelle."
Norwegian="Med denne programvaren kan du utføre ulike oppgaver etter at du har skannet et bilde og kontrollert filen, slik som å lagre bildet på datamaskinen, sende det med e-post, skrive det ut eller laste det opp til en FTP-server."
Swedish="Med detta program kan du utföra olika åtgärder efter det att en bild skannats och filen kontrollerats, du kan t.ex. spara bilden på datorn, sända den via e-post, skriva ut den eller överföra den till en FTP-server."
Polish="Ten program umożliwia wykonywanie różnych zadań po zeskanowaniu obrazu i sprawdzeniu pliku, takich jak zapisanie obrazu w komputerze, wysłanie obrazu w wiadomości e-mail, drukowanie lub przesłanie obrazu na serwer FTP."
Czech="Tento software vám umožňuje provádět různé úlohy po naskenování obrázku a kontrole souboru, například uložení obrázku do počítače, jeho odeslání e-mailem, tisk nebo odeslání na server FTP."
Hungarian="Ezzel a szoftverrel a kép beszkennelése és ellenőrzése után számos műveletet hajthat végre, úgy mint a kép mentése számítógépre, küldés e-mailben, nyomtatás vagy feltöltése egy FTP kiszolgálóra."
Slovakian="Tento softvér vám po naskenovaní obrázka a skontrolovaní súboru umožňuje vykonávať rôzne úlohy, ako napríklad uložiť obrázok do počítača, odoslať ho prostredníctvom e-mailu, vytlačiť ho alebo ho odovzdať na server FTP."
Romanian="Acest program software permite efectuarea diferitelor activităţi după scanarea unei imagini şi verificarea fişierului, de exemplu salvarea imaginii pe calculatorul dumneavoastră, trimiterea acesteia prin e-mail, imprimarea sau încărcarea imaginii pe un server FTP."
Bulgarian="Този софтуер ви позволява да изпълнявате различни задачи след сканиране на изображение и проверка на файла, като запазване на снимката в компютъра, изпращане по имейл, печат или качване на FTP сървър."
Latvian="Ar šo programmatūru pēc attēla skenēšanas un faila pārbaudes varēsit veikt dažādas darbības, piemēram, saglabāt attēlu datorā, sūtīt to, izmantojot e-pastu, drukāt vai augšupielādēt FTP serverī."
Lithuanian="Nuskaičius vaizdą ir patikrinus failą, ši programinė įranga leidžia atlikti įvairias užduotis, pvz., įrašyti vaizdą į kompiuterį, siųsti jį el. paštu, spausdinti arba įkelti į FTP serverį."
Estonian="See tarkvara võimaldab teil pärast pildi skannimist ja faili kontrollimist teostada mitmesuguseid toiminguid - te saate näiteks salvestada pildi arvutisse, saata seda e-posti teel, printida või FTP-serverisse üles laadida."
Catalan="Aquest programari permet dur a terme diverses tasques després d'escanejar una imatge i comprovar el fitxer, com ara desar la imatge a l'ordinador, enviar-la per correu electrònic, imprimir-la o pujar-la a un servidor FTP."
Russian="С помощью данного программного обеспечения можно выполнять различные задачи после сканирования изображения и проверки файла. Например, можно сохранить изображение на компьютер, отправить по электронной почте, распечатать или передать на FTP-сервер."
Ukrainian="За допомогою цього програмного забезпечення можна виконувати різні задачі після сканування зображення та перевірки файлу. Наприклад, можна зберегти зображення на комп'ютері, надіслати електронною поштою, надрукувати або передати на FTP-сервер."
Kazakh="Бұл бағдарламалық құрал суретті сканерлегеннен және файлды тексергеннен кейін суретті компьютеріңізге сақтау, оны электрондық поштамен жіберу, басып шығару немесе FTP серверіне жүктеу сияқты түрлі тапсырмаларды орындауға мүмкіндік береді."
Arabic="يتيح لك هذا البرنامج أداء العديد من المهام بعد مسح صورة ضوئيًا والتحقق من الملف، مثل حفظ الصورة في الكمبيوتر أو إرسالها عن طريق البريد الإلكتروني أو طباعتها أو تحميلها إلى خادم FTP."
Farsi="با استفاده این نرم افزار می توانید پس از اسکن کردن تصویر و بررسی فایل، کارهای مختلفی را انجام دهید، از جمله ذخیره تصویر در رایانه خود، ارسال آن از طریق ایمیل، چاپ کردن یا آپلود کردن آن در یک سرور FTP."
Korean="이 소프트웨어를 사용하여 이미지를 스캔하고 파일을 확인한 후 그 이미지를 컴퓨터에 저장, 이메일로 전송, 인쇄, FTP 서버에 업로드하는 등의 다양한 작업을 수행할 수 있습니다."
Thai="ซอฟต์แวร์นี้ทำให้ท่านสามารถปฏิบัติงานได้อย่างหลากหลายหลังจากสแกนรูปภาพและตรวจสอบไฟล์ เช่น บันทึกรูปภาพลงในคอมพิวเตอร์, ส่งทางอีเมล, พิมพ์ หรืออัพโหลดไปยังเซิร์ฟเวอร์ FTP"
Chinese="使用该软件，您可以在扫描图像并检查完文件后执行多种任务，例如将图像保存到计算机中、通过电子邮件发送、打印或者上传到 FTP 服务器。"
Taiwan="本軟體可讓您在掃描影像及檢查檔案之後執行各種工作，例如將影像儲存到電腦、透過電子郵件傳送、列印或上傳至 FTP 伺服器。"
Indonesian="Kelola dokumen yang dipindai dan simpan sebagai berkas, lalu kirim ke FTP, pencetak, atau awan."
Hebrew="נהל מסמכים סרוקים ושמור אותם כקבצים, ולאחר מכן שלח אותם ל-FTP, למדפסת או לענן."
Swahili="Simamia nyaraka zilizotambazwa na uzihifadhi kama faili, kisha uzitume kwa FTP, kichapishaji, au cloud."
Vietnamese="Q.lý các tài liệu đã scan và lưu chúng dạng file, sau đó gửi lên FTP, máy in hoặc kho lưu trữ đám mây."
Hindi="स्कैन किए गए दस्तावेज़ों का प्रबंधन करें और उन्हें फ़ाइल के रूप में सहेजें, फिर उन्हें FTP, प्रिंटर या क्लाउड पर भेजें।"
Turkmen="Skanirlenen programmalary dolandyryň we olary faýl görnüşinde ýazdyryň, soňra olary FTP, printere ýa-da bulut ulgamyna ugrat."
Belarussian="Кіруйце сканаванымі дакументамі і захоўвайце іх у выглядзе файлаў, потым дасылайце на FTP, прынтар ці ў воблака."
Azerbaijani="Skanlanmış sənədləri idarə edin və fayllar kimi saxlayın, sonra onları FTP, printer, və ya buluda göndərin."
Uzbek="Skanerlangan hujjatlarni boshqaring va fayl sifatida saqlang, ularni FTPga, printerga yoki bulutga jo'nating."
Mongolian="Сканнердсан документуудыг эмхэлж, файлаар хадгалж, FTP, принтер эсвэл үүл рүү илгээнэ."
Malay="Menguruskan dokumen yang diimbas dan menyimpannya sebagai fail, dan menghantarnya kepada FTP, pencetak atau awan."
Canadian_French="Gérer les documents numérisés et sauvegardez-les comme fichiers et ensuite, envoyez-les vers un site FTP, une imprimante ou le nuage."
Mexican_Spanish="Le permite gestionar documentos escaneados y guardarlos como archivos, para luego enviarlos a un sitio FTP, a una impresora o a la nube."
Brazilian_Portugues="Gerencie documentos digitalizados e salve-os como arquivos, depois os envie para FTP, uma impressora ou para a nuvem."
HongKong="本軟體可讓您在掃描影像及檢查檔案之後執行各種工作，例如將影像儲存到電腦、透過電子郵件傳送、列印或上傳至 FTP 伺服器。"
