[Common]
ApplicationName="Easy Photo Scan"
InstallFolderPath=%ProgramFiles%\Epson Software\Easy Photo Scan
SilentInstall=/qn
Installer=SETUP.EXE

RunServerOS=0

LastFirmVer=0

PrinterOnline=0

DefaultInstall=0
UpdateOnly=0

LocalInstaller="%AppPath%PhotoScan"

UpdateName="EasyPhotoScan"
UpdateCTI=61

[Japanese]
ApplicationName="Easy Photo Scan"

[ApplicationDescription]
Japanese="Easy Photo Scan（イージー フォト スキャン）では、スキャナーから原稿を読み込んで画像を確認後、画像編集/保存/メール送信/クラウドサービスへの転送などの操作ができます。"
English="Share and archive photos automatically to Facebook and Picasa."
French="Partagez et archivez vos photos automatiquement vers Facebook et Picasa."
German="Nach dem Scannen eines Bildes und dem Überprüfen der Datei, können Sie mit Easy Photo Scan verschiedene Aufgaben durchführen. Unter anderem können Sie das Bild bearbeiten, auf Ihrem Computer speichern, es per E-Mail versenden oder auf einen Cloud-Dienst hochladen."
Dutch="Nadat een afbeelding is gescand en het bestand is gecontroleerd, kunt u met Easy Photo Scan verschillende taken uitvoeren. Zo kunt u de afbeelding bewerken, opslaan, via e-mail versturen of naar een cloudservice uploaden."
Italian="Dopo lacquisizione di unimmagine e la verifica del file risultante, Easy Photo Scan consente di eseguire varie operazioni, ad esempio modificare limmagine, salvarla, inviarla tramite e-mail o caricarla in un servizio cloud."
Spanish="Comparta y guarde fotos automáticamente en Facebook y Picasa."
Portuguese="Compartilhe e arquive fotos automaticamente no Facebook e Picasa."
Turkish="Bir görüntüyü taradıktan ve dosyayı kontrol ettikten sonra Easy Photo Scan, görüntüyü düzenleme, görüntüyü kaydetme, e-postayla gönderme veya bir bulut hizmetine yükleme gibi çeşitli işlemleri gerçekleştirmenize imkan tanır."
Greek="Κοινοποιήστε και αρχειοθετήστε αυτόματα φωτογραφίες στο Facebook και το Picasa."
Slovenian="Samodejno delite in arhivirajte fotografije na Facebooku in v Picasi."
Croatian="Dijelite i arhivirajte fotografije automatski na web stranice Facebook i Picasa."
Macedonian="Споделувајте и архивирајте фотографии автоматски на Facebook и Picasa."
Serbian="Automatski delite i arhivirajte fotografije na mrežama Facebook i Picasa."
Danish="Del og gem automatisk fotos til Facebook og Picasa."
Finnish="Jaa ja arkistoi valokuvia automaattisesti Facebookiin ja Picasaan."
Norwegian="Del og lagre bilder automatisk på Facebook og Picasa."
Swedish="Dela och arkivera foton automatiskt med Facebook och Picasa."
Polish="Po zeskanowaniu obrazu i sprawdzeniu pliku program Easy Photo Scan umożliwia wykonanie różnych zadań, np. edycję obrazu, zapisanie obrazu, wysłanie obrazu za pomocą poczty elektronicznej lub przesłanie do usługi chmury."
Czech="Po naskenování obrazu a zkontrolování souboru vám software Easy Photo Scan umožní provést řadu úkonů, jako například úpravu obrazu, uložení obrazu, jeho odeslání e-mailem nebo nahrání do služby cloud."
Hungarian="A kép beolvasása és a fájl kijelölése után az Easy Photo Scan lehetővé teszi, hogy különféle műveleteket végezzen, akár a kép szerkesztését, mentését, küldését e-mailben vagy feltöltését felhőszolgáltatásra."
Slovakian="Zdieľajte a archivujte fotografie automaticky prostredníctvom služieb Facebook a Picasa."
Romanian="După scanarea unei imagini şi verificarea fişierului, Easy Photo Scan vă permite să efectuaţi diverse sarcini, precum editarea sau salvarea imaginii, trimiterea acesteia prin e-mail sau încărcarea pe un serviciu tip cloud."
Bulgarian="Споделяйте и архивирайте снимки автоматично във Facebook и Picasa."
Latvian="Automātiski koplietojiet un arhivējiet fotoattēlus vietnēs Facebook un Picasa."
Lithuanian="Dalykitės ir archyvuokite nuotraukas automatiškai svetainėse „Facebook“ ir „Picasa“."
Estonian="Jagage fotosid automaatselt sotsiaalrakenduses Facebook ja programmis Picasa ning arhiveerige neid seal."
Catalan="Compartiu i arxiveu fotografies automàticament al Facebook i al Picasa."
Russian="Автоматически делитесь фотографиями и архивируйте их на Facebook и Picasa."
Ukrainian="Обмінюйтеся фотографіями та архівуйте їх автоматично в службах Facebook і Picasa."
Kazakh="Фотосуреттерді автоматты түрде Facebook және Picasa қызметтерінде бөлісіңіз және мұрағаттаңыз."
Arabic="يمكنك مشاركة الصور وأرشفتها تلقائيًا إلى Facebook وPicasa."
Farsi="عکس ها را بطور خودکار در Facebook و Picasa به اشتراک بگذارید و بایگانی کنید."
Korean="이미지를 스캔하고 확인한 후 Easy Photo Scan에서 이미지를 편집, 저장, 이메일로 전송, 클라우드 서비스로 업로딩 하는 등의 다양한 작업을 실행할 수 있습니다."
Thai="After scanning an image and checking the file, Easy Photo Scan allows you to perform various tasks such as editing the image, saving the image, sending it by email, or uploading to a cloud service."
Chinese="在扫描图像和检查文件后，Easy Photo Scan允许您执行各项工作，如：编辑图像、保存图像、通过邮件发送或上传到一个云服务。"
Taiwan="掃描影像並檢查檔案後，Easy Photo Scan 允許您執行各種工作，例如編輯影像、儲存影像、透過電子郵件傳送或上傳至雲端服務。"
Indonesian="Bagi dan simpan foto secara otomatis ke Facebook dan Picasa."
Hebrew="שתף תמונות ושמור אותן באופן אוטומטי ב-Facebook ו-Picasa."
Swahili="Shiriki na uhifadhii picha kiotomatiki kwenye Facebook na Picasa."
Vietnamese="Chia sẻ và lưu trữ ảnh chụp tự động lên Facebook và Picasa."
Hindi="फोटो को स्वचालित रूप से Facebook और Picasa पर शेयर करें तथा अभिलेखित करें।"
Turkmen="Fotosuratlary awtomatik usulda Facebook-da hem Picasa-da paýlaş we arhiwine ýerleşdir."
Belarussian="Аўтаматычна дзяліцеся і захоўвайце фота на Facebook і Picasa."
Azerbaijani="Şəkilləri avtomatik olaraq Facebook və Picasa ilə paylaşın və arxivləşdirin."
Uzbek="Fotosuratlarni avtomatik ravishda Facebook va Picasa orqali ulashing hamda arxivlang."
Mongolian="Фото зургийг автоматаар Facebook болон Picasa-д хуваалцаж архивлана."
Malay="Kongsi gambar yang diarkib secara automatik kepada Facebook dan Picasa."
Canadian_French="Partagez et archivez vos photos automatiquement vers Facebook et Picasa."
Mexican_Spanish="Comparta y guarde fotos automáticamente en Facebook y Picasa."
Brazilian_Portugues="Compartilhe e arquive fotos automaticamente no Facebook e Picasa."
HongKong="掃描影像並檢查檔案後，Easy Photo Scan 允許您執行各種工作，例如編輯影像、儲存影像、透過電子郵件傳送或上傳至雲端服務。"
