[Common]
ApplicationName="Photo+"
InstallFolderPath=%ProgramFiles%\Epson Software\PhotoPlus
SilentInstall=/q
Installer=SETUP.EXE

RunServerOS=0

LastFirmVer=0

PrinterOnline=0

DefaultInstall=0
UpdateOnly=0

LocalInstaller="%AppPath%PhotoPlusXV"

UpdateName="PhotoPlus"
UpdateCTI=61

SupportOS="Winnt51;Winnt51.x64;Winnt60;Winnt60.x64"

[ApplicationDescription]
Japanese="写真に文字やスタンプを重ねたり、多彩なテンプレートと組み合わせて簡単に印刷できます。"
English="You can add letters and stamps on the photo and print it easily with a variety of templates."
French="Ce logiciel vous permet de disposer et d'imprimer des images numeriques sur differents types de papier avec differents reglages et differentes ameliorations."
German="Mit dieser Software konnen Sie digitale Bilder bearbeiten und auf verschiedenen Papierarten ausdrucken."
Dutch="Met deze software kunt u digitale afbeeldingen opmaken en afdrukken op verschillende soorten papier met diverse instelmogelijkheden."
Italian="Questo software consente di disporre e stampare immagini digitali su diversi tipi di carta con varie regolazioni e ottimizzazioni."
Spanish="Este software le permite componer e imprimir imagenes digitales en papeles de diversos tipos con diversos ajustes y mejoras."
Portuguese="Este software permite-lhe esquematizar e imprimir imagens digitais em varios tipos de papel com varios ajustes e efeitos."
Turkish="Bu yaz?l?m, dijital resimleri de?i?ik ayar ve geli?tirmeler ile birlikte ce?itli tipte ka??tlara yerle?tirip basman?z? sa?lar."
Greek="Αυτ? το λογισμικ? σα? επιτρ?πει να διατ?ζετε και να εκτυπ?νετε ψηφιακ?? εικ?νε? σε δι?φορου? τ?που? χαρτιο? με δι?φορε? αναπροσαρμογ?? και βελτι?σει?."
Slovenian="S to programsko opremo lahko tiskate digitalne podobe na razne tipe papirja z raznimi prilagoditvami in oja?itvami."
Croatian="Ovaj softver Vam omogu?ava da uredite i ispi?ete digitalne slike na razli?itim vrstama papira, uz razli?ita pode?enja i pobolj?anja."
Macedonian="Софтверот овозможува распоредува?е и печате?е дигитални слики на разни видови хартии со разни прилагодува?а и подобрува?а."
Serbian="Ovaj softver omogu?ava raspore?ivanje i ?tampanje digitalnih slika na raznim vrstama papira uz brojna pode?avanja i pobolj?anja."
Danish="Denne software giver dig mulighed for at designe og udskrive digitale billeder pa forskellige typer papir med forskellige justeringer og forbedring."
Finnish="Taman ohjelmiston avulla voit tehda eri asetteluja ja tulostaa digitaalikuvia erityyppisille papereille soveltaen erilaisia saatoja ja parannuksia."
Norwegian="Med denne programvaren kan du plassere og skrive ut digitale bilder pa en rekke forskjellige papirtyper med ulike justeringer og forbedringer."
Swedish="Med programmet kan du gora layout och skriva ut digitala bilder pa olika papperstyper med diverse installningar och forbattringar."
Polish="Ten program pozwala rozplanowa? i wydrukowa? zdj?cia cyfrowe na ro?nych typach papieru przy u?yciu wielu zmian i udoskonale?."
Czech="Tento software vam umo?ni sestavit a vytisknout digitalni obrazky na r?zne typy papiru s r?znymi upravami a vylep?enim."
Hungarian="Ezzel a szoftverrel elrendezhet es nyomtathat digitalis kepeket kulonfele papirokra szamos beallitassal es fejlesztessel."
Slovakian="Tento softver vam umo?ni zostavi? a vytla?i? digitalne obrazky na rozne typy papiera s roznymi upravami a vylep?enim."
Romanian="Acest program v? permite s? afi?a?i ?i s? tip?ri?i imagini digitale pe diverse tipuri de hartie cu diverse regl?ri ?i func?ii."
Bulgarian="Този софтуер ви позволява да разполагате и печатате цифрови изображения върху различни типове хартия с различни настройки и увеличения."
Latvian="?? programmat?ra ?auj izk?rtot un druk?t ciparu att?lus uz da??da tipa pap?ra ar neskait?m?m uzlabo?anas un piel?go?anas iesp?j?m."
Lithuanian="?i ?ranga leid?ia maketuoti ir spausdinti skaitmeninius vaizdus ant ?vairi? tip? popieri? su ?vairiais nustatymais ir korekcijomis."
Estonian="Selle tarkvaraga saate digipilte kuljendada ja printida erinevat tuupi paberile erinevate satete ja efektidega."
Catalan="Aquest programari us permet dissenyar i imprimir imatges digitals en diversos tipus de paper amb diversos ajustaments i millores."
Russian="Это программное обеспечение позволяет вам компоновать и печатать цифровые изображения на бумаге различного типа с разными настройками и оптимизацией."
Ukrainian="Це ПЗ дозволя? розташовувати ? друкувати цифров? зображення на папер? р?зних тип?в, з р?зними вдосконаленнями."
Kazakh="Осы ба?дарламамен с?з цифрл? суреттерд? т?рл? ?а?аздар?а ?р?илы жа?сандырумен ж?не ?згертумен басу болады."
Arabic="???? ?? ??? ???????? ????? ?????? ??? ????? ??? ????? ?????? ?? ????? ?? ???????? ????? ??????? ??????????."
Farsi="?? ??? ??? ??? ????? ?? ?????? ?? ??????? ?? ??????? ?????? ???? ???? ?????? ??????? ?? ?? ??? ????? ????? ???? ????? ????."
Korean="?? ??? ?? ? ??? ??? ??? ???? ??? ? ?? ????????."
Thai="?????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????? ?????????????????????????????????"
Chinese="本?件??可通?多??整和增?操作将数??像布局并打印到各??型的??上。"
Taiwan="此軟體可讓?以不同的校正和增強方式，在不同種類的紙張上配置和列印數位影像。"
Indonesian="Edit, perbesar, sesuaikan, dan cetak foto Anda"
Hebrew="????, ????, ???? ????? ????? ?? ??????? ???"
Swahili="Hariri, ongeza ukubwa, geuza kukufaa na chapisha picha zako"
Vietnamese="S??a, pho?ng to, tu?y chi?nh va? in a?nh chu?p cu?a ba?n"
Hindi="???? ????? ?? ???????, ????, ????????? ?? ?????? ?????"
Turkmen="Fotosuratlary?yzy uytgedi?, ulaldy?, ozle?diri? we cap edi?"
Belarussian="Рэдагуйце, павял?чвайце, дапасо?вайце ? друкуйце фота"
Azerbaijani="??kill?rinizi redakt? edin, geni?l?ndirin, f?rdil??dirin v? cap edin"
Uzbek="Fotosuratlaringizni tahrirlang, kattalashtiring, moslashtiring va chop eting"
Mongolian="Фото зургаа засч, томсгож, ??рчилж, хэвлэ"
Malay="Edit, besarkan, menyesuaikan, dan cetak gambar anda"
Canadian_French="Partagez et archivez vos photos automatiquement vers Facebook et Picasa.
"
Mexican_Spanish="Comparta y guarde fotos automaticamente en Facebook y Picasa.
"
Brazilian_Portugues="Compartilhe e arquive fotos automaticamente no Facebook e Picasa.
"
HongKong="掃描影像並檢??案後，Easy Photo Scan 允許?執行各種工作，例如編輯影像、儲存影像、透過電子郵件傳送或上傳至雲端服務。
"
