[Common]
ApplicationName="Copy Utility"
InstallFolderPath=%ProgramFiles%\Epson Software\Copy Utility
SilentInstall=/qn
Installer=SETUP.EXE

RunServerOS=0

LastFirmVer=0

PrinterOnline=0

DefaultInstall=1
UpdateOnly=0

LocalInstaller="%AppPath%CopyUtility"

UpdateName="CopyUty"
UpdateCTI=61

[Japanese]
ApplicationName="Copy Utility"

[ApplicationDescription]
Japanese="スキャナー、コンピューター、プリンターを連携して、画像のコピーや写真の焼き増しができます。 "
English="This software lets you use your all-in-one product connected to your computer just like a copy machine."
French="Ce logiciel vous permet d'utiliser le combiné multifonction connecté à l'ordinateur comme un photocopieur."
German="Mit dieser Software können Sie Ihr an den PC angeschlossenes All-in-one-Produkt als Kopierer verwenden."
Dutch="Met deze software kunt u uw alles-in-één-apparaat (aangesloten op uw computer) gebruiken als kopieerapparaat."
Italian="Questo software consente di utilizzare il prodotto multifunzione collegato al computer come un'apparecchiatura fotocopiatrice."
Spanish="Este software le permite utilizar su producto "todo en uno" conectado a su ordenador como si fuera una copiadora."
Portuguese="Este software permite-lhe utilizar o produto multifunções ligado ao computador como uma fotocopiadora."
Turkish="Bu yazılım, bilgisayarınıza bağlı olan hepsi bir arada ürününüzü bir fotokopi makinesi gibi kullanabilmenizi sağlar."
Greek="Αυτό το λογισμικό σας επιτρέπει να χρησιμοποιείτε το προϊόν σας "όλα σε ένα" που είναι συνδεδεμένο με τον υπολογιστή σας όπως ένα αντιγραφικό μηχάνημα."
Slovenian="S to programsko opremo lahko uporabljate vaš vse-v-enem izdelek povezan na vaš računalnik kot kopirni stroj."
Croatian="Ovaj softver Vam omogućava da svoj višenamjenski uređaj koji je spojen na Vaše računalo, koristite kao uobičajeni uređaj za fotokopiranje."
Macedonian="Софтверот ви овозможува да го користите комбинираниот производ приклучен во компјутерот како фотокопир."
Serbian="Ovaj softver omogućava korišćenje kombinovanog uređaja priključenog na računar kao fotokopir-mašine."
Danish="Denne software giver dig mulighed for at bruge dit alt-i-et-produkt tilsluttet din computer nøjagtigt som en kopimaskine."
Finnish="Tämän ohjelmiston avulla voit käyttää tietokoneeseen kytkettyä monitoimilaitetta kopiokoneen tavoin."
Norwegian="Med denne programvaren kan du bruke alt-i-ett-produktet som er koblet til datamaskinen, som en vanlig kopimaskin."
Swedish="Med programmet kan allt-i-ett-produkten användas som en kopiator när den är ansluten till en dator."
Polish="Ten program pozwala na używanie wszechstronnego produktu podłączonego do komputera jako kopiarki."
Czech="Tento software vám umožní použití komplexního výrobku připojeného k vašemu počítači stejně jako kopírky."
Hungarian="Ezzel a szoftverrel használhatja a számítógéphez csatlakoztatott 'minden egyben' készülékét, például a másológépet."
Slovakian="Tento softvér vám umožní použitie komplexného výrobku pripojeného k vášmu počítaču rovnako ako kopírky."
Romanian="Acest program vă permite să utilizaţi produsul all-in-one conectat la calculator, asemenea unui copiator."
Bulgarian="Този софтуер ви позволява да използвате вашия продукт 'всичко в едно', свързан към вашия компютър, просто като копирна машина."
Latvian="Šī programmatūra ļauj izmantot jūsu daudzfunkcionālo izstrādājumu, pievienojot datoram tāpat, kā kopētāju."
Lithuanian="Ši įranga leidžia naudoti prie kompiuterio prijungtą daugiafunkcį įrenginį kaip kopijavimo aparatą."
Estonian="Selle tarkvaraga saate kasutada seda arvutiga ühendatud universaalset toodet koopiamasinana."
Catalan="Aquest programari us permet utilitzar el vostre producte tot en un connectat a l'ordinador com si fos una fotocopiadora."
Russian="Это программное обеспечение позволяет использовать многофункциональное устройство, подключенное к вашему компьютеру, в качестве копировальной машины."
Ukrainian="Це ПЗ дозволяє використовувати БФА, підключений до комп'ютера, як ксерокс."
Kazakh="Осы бағдарлама сізге бәрі-бірде көшіру машина сияқты сіздің компьютерге қосылған өнімді береді."
Arabic="يتيح لك هذا البرنامج استخدام منتج all-in-one‏ ‏المتصل بالكمبيوتر على أنه مكنة تصوير."
Farsi="این نرم افزار به شما امكان می دهد تا از دستگاه چند منظوره خود بصورت متصل به رایانه و مانند یك دستگاه كپی استفاده كنید."
Korean="이 소프트웨어를 통해 컴퓨터에 연결된 복합기 제품을 복사기처럼 사용할 수 있습니다."
Thai="ซอฟต์แวร์นี้ทำให้ท่านใช้ผลิตภัณฑ์ all-in-one ของท่านเชื่อมต่อกับคอมพิวเตอร์ได้เหมือนกับเครื่องถ่ายสำเนา"
Chinese="本软件让您可将连接至计算机的多功能一体机产品用作复印机。"
Taiwan="此軟體可讓您使用連接至電腦的多功能複合機，就像是影印機一樣。"
Indonesian="Salin dokumen atau foto menggunakan komputer, printer, dan pemindai."
Hebrew="צילום מסמכים או תמונות באמצעות המחשב, המדפסת והסורק."
Swahili="Nakili hati au picha kwa kutumia kompyuta, printa, na kitambazo chako."
Vietnamese="Sao chụp các tài liệu hoặc ảnh chụp bằng máy tính, máy in và máy scan."
Hindi="अपने कंप्यूटर, प्रिंटर और स्कैनर का उपयोग करते हुए दस्तावेज़ों या फ़ोटो की प्रति बनाएँ।"
Turkmen="Kompýuteriňizi, printeriňizi we skaneriňizi ulanyp dokumentleriňizi ýa-da suratlaryňyzy göçüriň."
Belarussian="Рабіце копіі дакументаў ці фота з дапамогай камп&apos;ютара, прынтара і сканера."
Azerbaijani="Kompüterinizdən, printerinizdən və skanerinizdən istifadə etməklə sənədləri və ya şəkilləri köçürün."
Uzbek="Kompyuter, printer va skaner yordamida hujjatlar hamda fotosuratlarni nusxalang."
Mongolian="Компьютер, принтер болон сканнераа ашиглан баримт эсвэл фотог хуулбарла."
Malay="Salin dokumen atau foto menggunakan komputer, pencetak dan pengimbas anda."
Canadian_French="Copier les documents ou les photos en utilisant votre ordinateur, votre imprimante et votre scanner."
Mexican_Spanish="Copie documentos o fotos utilizando su PC, impresora y escáner."
Brazilian_Portugues="Copie documentos ou fotografias, utilizando o seu computador, impressora e scanner."
HongKong="使用您的電腦、印表機及掃描器複印文件或相片。"
